[
	{
		"question": "What was Faust called in the older Guilty Gear titles?",
		"answer1": "Dr.Baldhead",
		"answer2": "Mr.James",
		"answer3": "Col.Sanders",
		"answer4": "Mr.Simon",
		"correct": 1
	},
	
	{
		"question": "Who is Kliff Undersn's foster child?",
		"answer1": "Ky",
		"answer2": "Chipp",
		"answer3": "Testament",
		"answer4": "Tyr",
		"correct": 3
	},
	
	{
		"question": "What animal does May call upon when activating one of her super moves in Strive?",
		"answer1": "Dolphin",
		"answer2": "Whale",
		"answer3": "Shark",
		"answer4": "Otter",
		"correct": 2
	},
	
	{
		"question": "Which Queen album does Sol Badguy love listening to?",
		"answer1": "Made in Heaven",
		"answer2": "The Game",
		"answer3": "News of the World",
		"answer4": "Sheer Heart Attack",
		"correct": 4
	},
	
	{
		"question": "What position of power does Chipp the ninja eventually want to obtain?",
		"answer1": "King",
		"answer2": "Assassin's Syndicate Leader",
		"answer3": "President",
		"answer4": "Baker",
		"correct": 3
	},
	
	{
		"question": "How tall is Faust?",
		"answer1": "9'3",
		"answer2": "10'2",
		"answer3": "8'5",
		"answer4": "6'8",
		"correct": 1
	},
	
	{
		"question": "What is one of Faust's favourite hobbies?",
		"answer1": "Smoking and drinking",
		"answer2": "Polishing his favourite scalpel",
		"answer3": "Collecting high quality paper bags",
		"answer4": "Performing dissections",
		"correct": 3
	},
	
	{
		"question": "What’s the name of Axl Low’s girlfriend?",
		"answer1": "Aria",
		"answer2": "Megumi",
		"answer3": "Catherine",
		"answer4": "Elizabeth",
		"correct": 2
	},
	
	{
		"question": "What is one of Giovanna’s pet peeves?",
		"answer1": "Cats",
		"answer2": "Having to wait too long in line",
		"answer3": "Getting interrupted when she speaks",
		"answer4": "The smell of cigarettes and alcohol",
		"correct": 4
	},
	
	{
		"question": "What alias refers to Jack-O when she was still serving 'That Man?'",
		"answer1": "Jupiter",
		"answer2": "Juno",
		"answer3": "Jill",
		"answer4": "Jack the Reaper",
		"correct": 2
	},
	
	{
		"question": "Which resource does Happy Chaos consume when summoning a clone?",
		"answer1": "Bar",
		"answer2": "Health",
		"answer3": "Focus",
		"answer4": "Ammo",
		"correct": 2
	},
	
	{
		"question": "What odd object does Strive’s Baiken dislike?",
		"answer1": "Garden Gnomes",
		"answer2": "Pencils",
		"answer3": "Kalimbas",
		"answer4": "Raccoon Ornaments",
		"correct": 4
	},
	
	{
		"question": "How much does Potemkin weigh?",
		"answer1": "211 kg",
		"answer2": "521 kg",
		"answer3": "1211 kg",
		"answer4": "3000 kg",
		"correct": 3
	},
	
	{
		"question": "Which everyday object does Potemkin have an infatuation with?",
		"answer1": "Pencils",
		"answer2": "Shoes",
		"answer3": "Water Bottles",
		"answer4": "Wallets",
		"correct": 1
	},
	
	{
		"question": "What juice is Nagoriyuki’s favourite?",
		"answer1": "Apple Juice",
		"answer2": "Tomato Juice",
		"answer3": "Banana Juice",
		"answer4": "Grape Juice",
		"correct": 2
	},
	
	{
		"question": "Which country is Millia Rage from?",
		"answer1": "Germany",
		"answer2": "Sweden",
		"answer3": "France",
		"answer4": "Russia",
		"correct": 4
	}
]